street-gals.com 2010-11-20

# street-gals.com

At street-gals.com, we respect our customers and understand that you are concerned about privacy, so we've instituted policies intended to ensure that your personal information is handled safely and responsibly.

  1\. The information street-gals.com collect is limited to your numerical IP address assigned to your computer by your Internet Service Provider and your E-mail Address. Neither street-gals.com nor our affiliate stores your credit card processing information. It is securely stored by our service organizations, depending on the billing company you selected at the time you made your transaction.

  2\. When you visit street-gals.com, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends such as your web request, IP address, browser type, browser language, referring URL, platform type, domain names and the date and time of your request. We may utilize this information to provide you with better services by analyzing trend of our users.

  3\. It is your obligation to provide street-gals.com with accurate and up-to date information, and failure to do so could void any Agreement between you and each of street-gals.com's hosting web sites which you have entered into to acquire services. street-gals.com uses the information that you provide for such purposes as processing your credit card transaction, loss prevention, improving our service, communicating with you, and allowing our affiliates to provide customer service and fulfill their obligations to you. street-gals.com ensure that such affiliates and street-gals.com have both agreed mutually to NDA ( Non-Disclosure Agreement ) in advance.

  4\. The employees at street-gals.com have access to user information on a need-to-know basis, in order to control the safety of the personal data to the extent necessary and appropriate.

  5\. street-gals.com may release and disclose confidential and sensitive information to the extent necessary to respond to a valid order by a court or other governmental body as street-gals.com receives a court order, or is otherwise required by law to disclose any such information. Otherwise street-gals.com will never sell your information to an independent third party for any reason nor will knowingly provide your credit card or bank account information outside of this system.

  6\. street-gals.com employs the latest and best techniques available for protecting its systems from intrusion by unauthorized individuals, and is constantly upgrading its security as better methods become available. All information is stored behind firewalls and other sophisticated security systems. In addition, our data center utilizes state-of-the-art physical security measures to prevent unauthorized access to the facility.

  7\. The Privacy Policy may be changed by street-gals.com from time to time as we determine its appropriate to do so. It is solely your responsibility to check Privacy Policy for frequent changes. Unless otherwise explicitly stated herein, all changes shall become effective upon posting on this Privacy Policy. 

  Maxx International, Inc.  
28375 Ventura Blvd. #103 Calabasas,   
California 91302 United States
